{
  "date": "2026-01-05",
  "dayOfWeek": "Monday",
  "weekNumber": "2",
  "quarter": "1",
  "timestamp": "2026-01-05T13:53:33.435Z",
  "todayMessage": "Taking off starts with being present. Let go of the control. You know who actually controls. Just act, while being here. ",
  "goals": [
    "Get the week and month set",
    "Catch up of the list",
    "Connect with people "
  ],
  "tasks": [
    {
      "text": "",
      "completed": true
    },
    {
      "text": "",
      "completed": true
    },
    {
      "text": "",
      "completed": true
    }
  ],
  "reachOut": [
    "Olivia",
    "Sarah ",
    "Leads "
  ],
  "prompts": [
    {
      "prompt": "One thing I can get excited about today is...",
      "response": "How wide open my day is. Nothing is keeping me attached today but me "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "A positive phrase or sentence I can say to myself several times today is...",
      "response": "Are you here, right now? "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Someone who needs me on my A-game today is...",
      "response": "The universe "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "A situation that might stress me out or trip me up today could be...",
      "response": "Principals needing me "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "...and the way that my best self would deal with that is...",
      "response": "Stay present and do it. You have all the \"time\" in the world "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Someone I could surprise with a note, gift, or sign of appreciation is...",
      "response": "AS"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "One action I could take today to demonstrate excellence or real value is...",
      "response": "Completion, action and follow through on tasks - seems small, but so important for the energy shift needed for takeoff "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "One bold action I could take today is...",
      "response": "Today is not a bold day - but I would say the circle process weekly problem solving to possibility "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "If I was my own high performance coach, I would tell myself this today...",
      "response": "Stay present, be being :) "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I would complete this day proud of my efforts if I make sure I...",
      "response": "Connect with the people above and follow through on the list of fun and managing type stuff "
    },
    {
      "prompt": "The big picture I have to keep in mind today is that I am working steadily towards...",
      "response": "All of my work today, the thoughts, actions, products, and connections are fueling the Interior Architect of Transformation. "
    }
  ],
  "schedule": [
    {
      "time": "06:00",
      "activity": "Sweat, Stretch and Ready ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "07:30",
      "activity": "Journal and List of tasks ",
      "domain": "career"
    },
    {
      "time": "08:00",
      "activity": "Tasks ",
      "domain": "creative"
    },
    {
      "time": "08:30",
      "activity": "Tasks",
      "domain": "career"
    },
    {
      "time": "09:00",
      "activity": "Person 1 - Sarah ",
      "domain": "career"
    },
    {
      "time": "09:30",
      "activity": "Snap wife ",
      "domain": "love"
    },
    {
      "time": "10:00",
      "activity": "Person 2 - Olivia ",
      "domain": "career"
    },
    {
      "time": "11:00",
      "activity": "Group 3 - Leads ",
      "domain": "career"
    },
    {
      "time": "11:30",
      "activity": "Snap Wife ",
      "domain": "love"
    },
    {
      "time": "12:00",
      "activity": "Task",
      "domain": "creative"
    },
    {
      "time": "14:00",
      "activity": "Finances - Problem to possibility - short term ",
      "domain": "money"
    },
    {
      "time": "14:30",
      "activity": "Finances - Long term ",
      "domain": "money"
    },
    {
      "time": "15:00",
      "activity": "Finances - Long Term ",
      "domain": "money"
    },
    {
      "time": "15:30",
      "activity": "Home ",
      "domain": ""
    },
    {
      "time": "16:00",
      "activity": "Work out ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "16:30",
      "activity": "Work out ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "17:00",
      "activity": "Dinner ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "17:30",
      "activity": "Sweat ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "18:00",
      "activity": "Stretch ",
      "domain": "health"
    },
    {
      "time": "18:30",
      "activity": "Recap, Relax ",
      "domain": "inner"
    },
    {
      "time": "19:00",
      "activity": "Kids ",
      "domain": "love"
    }
  ],
  "habits": {
    "clarity": 8,
    "energy": 8,
    "necessity": 7,
    "productivity": 9,
    "influence": 5,
    "courage": 9,
    "overall": 7.7
  },
  "domains": {
    "money": {
      "progress": false,
      "notes": ""
    },
    "health": {
      "progress": true,
      "notes": ""
    },
    "career": {
      "progress": true,
      "notes": ""
    },
    "creative": {
      "progress": true,
      "notes": ""
    },
    "love": {
      "progress": true,
      "notes": ""
    },
    "inner": {
      "progress": true,
      "notes": ""
    }
  },
  "pathAllocation": 50,
  "wins": [
    "Tasks complete",
    "Short term financed done",
    "Shipped one idea"
  ],
  "improvement": "TBD ",
  "gratitude": "I am grateful for now ",
  "tomorrowPriority": "Ship"
}